[
  {
    "question": "Accommodate",
    "answer": "容納"
  },
  {
    "question": "Acquire",
    "answer": "獲得"
  },
  {
    "question": "Adequate",
    "answer": "足夠的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Adjust",
    "answer": "調整"
  },
  {
    "question": "Administration",
    "answer": "行政"
  },
  {
    "question": "Advance",
    "answer": "前進"
  },
  {
    "question": "Agenda",
    "answer": "議程"
  },
  {
    "question": "Allocate",
    "answer": "分配"
  },
   {
    "question": "Ambitious",
    "answer": "有野心的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Annual",
    "answer": "年度的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Anticipate",
    "answer": "預期"
  },
  {
    "question": "Appoint",
    "answer": "任命"
  },
  {
    "question": "Appreciate",
    "answer": "感謝"
  },
  {
    "question": "Assemble",
    "answer": "組裝"
  },
  {
    "question": "Assess",
    "answer": "評估"
  },
  {
    "question": "Assign",
    "answer": "分配"
  },
  {
    "question": "Assist",
    "answer": "協助"
  },
  {
    "question": "Assume",
    "answer": "假設"
  },
  {
    "question": "Authorize",
    "answer": "授權"
  },
  {
    "question": "Available",
    "answer": "可用的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Awareness",
    "answer": "意識"
  },
  {
    "question": "Bargain",
    "answer": "議價"
  },
  {
    "question": "Beneficial",
    "answer": "有益的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Budget",
    "answer": "預算"
  },
  {
    "question": "Calculate",
    "answer": "計算"
  },
  {
    "question": "Capacity",
    "answer": "容量"
  },
  {
    "question": "Career",
    "answer": "職業"
  },
  {
    "question": "Cautious",
    "answer": "謹慎的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Celebrate",
    "answer": "慶祝"
  },
  {
    "question": "Certificate",
    "answer": "證書"
  },
  {
    "question": "Characteristic",
    "answer": "特徵"
  },
  {
    "question": "Charge",
    "answer": "收費"
  },
  {
    "question": "Circumstances",
    "answer": "情況"
  },
  {
    "question": "Claim",
    "answer": "聲稱"
  },
  {
    "question": "Client",
    "answer": "客戶"
  },
  {
    "question": "Collaborate",
    "answer": "合作"
  },
  {
    "question": "Colleague",
    "answer": "同事"
  },
  {
    "question": "Communicate",
    "answer": "溝通"
  },
  {
    "question": "Company",
    "answer": "公司"
  },
  {
    "question": "Compensate",
    "answer": "賠償"
  },
  {
    "question": "Competent",
    "answer": " компетентний"
  },
  {
    "question": "Competition",
    "answer": "競爭"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complain",
    "answer": "抱怨"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete",
    "answer": "完成"
  },
  {
    "question": "Complex",
    "answer": "複雜的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Comply",
    "answer": "遵守"
  },
  {
    "question": "Comprehensive",
    "answer": "全面的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Compulsory",
    "answer": "義務的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Concern",
    "answer": "關心"
  },
  {
    "question": "Conclude",
    "answer": "結論"
  },
  {
    "question": "Conduct",
    "answer": "行為"
  },
  {
    "question": "Confirm",
    "answer": "確認"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consequence",
    "answer": "後果"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider",
    "answer": "考慮"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consistent",
    "answer": "一致的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Constant",
    "answer": "恆定的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Construction",
    "answer": "建設"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consult",
    "answer": "諮詢"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consumer",
    "answer": "消費者"
  },
  {
    "question": "Contract",
    "answer": "合約"
  },
  {
    "question": "Contribute",
    "answer": "貢獻"
  },
  {
    "question": "Control",
    "answer": "控制"
  },
  {
    "question": "Convenient",
    "answer": "方便的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Convince",
    "answer": "說服"
  },
  {
    "question": "Corporate",
    "answer": "公司的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Cost",
    "answer": "成本"
  },
  {
    "question": "Credit",
    "answer": "信用"
  },
  {
    "question": "Criteria",
    "answer": "標準"
  },
  {
    "question": "Critical",
    "answer": "重要的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Currency",
    "answer": "貨幣"
  },
  {
     "question": "Custom",
    "answer": "習俗"
  },
  {
    "question": "Customer",
    "answer": "顧客"
  },
  {
    "question": "Damage",
    "answer": "損害"
  },
  {
    "question": "Deadline",
    "answer": "截止日期"
  },
  {
    "question": "Deal",
    "answer": "交易"
  },
  {
    "question": "Debit",
    "answer": "借方"
  },
  {
    "question": "Debt",
    "answer": "債務"
  },
  {
    "question": "Decision",
    "answer": "決定"
  },
  {
    "question": "Decrease",
    "answer": "減少"
  },
  {
    "question": "Deduct",
    "answer": "扣除"
  },
  {
    "question": "Defect",
    "answer": "缺陷"
  },
  {
     "question": "Defective",
    "answer": "有缺陷的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Delay",
    "answer": "延遲"
  },
  {
    "question": "Delegate",
    "answer": "委派"
  },
  {
    "question": "Deliver",
    "answer": "交付"
  },
  {
    "question": "Demand",
    "answer": "需求"
  },
  {
    "question": "Demanding",
    "answer": "苛求的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Demonstrate",
    "answer": "展示"
  },
  {
    "question": "Department",
    "answer": "部門"
  },
  {
    "question": "Departure",
    "answer": "出發"
  },
  {
    "question": "Deposit",
    "answer": "存款"
  },
  {
    "question": "Describe",
    "answer": "描述"
  },
   {
    "question": "Designate",
    "answer": "指定"
  },
  {
    "question": "Desperate",
    "answer": "絕望的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Destination",
    "answer": "目的地"
  },
  {
    "question": "Detail",
    "answer": "細節"
  },
  {
    "question": "Detect",
    "answer": "察覺"
  },
  {
    "question": "Determine",
    "answer": "確定"
  },
  {
    "question": "Develop",
    "answer": "發展"
  },
  {
    "question": "Device",
    "answer": "裝置"
  },
  {
    "question": "Diagnose",
    "answer": "診斷"
  },
  {
    "question": "Difference",
    "answer": "差異"
  },
  {
    "question": "Direct",
    "answer": "直接的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Director",
    "answer": "主管"
  },
  {
    "question": "Disagree",
    "answer": "不同意"
  },
  {
    "question": "Disappointing",
    "answer": "令人失望的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Discount",
    "answer": "折扣"
  },
  {
    "question": "Discuss",
    "answer": "討論"
  },
  {
    "question": "Dismiss",
    "answer": "解僱"
  },
  {
    "question": "Display",
    "answer": "展示"
  },
  {
    "question": "Dispose",
    "answer": "處理"
  },
  {
    "question": "Dispute",
    "answer": "爭端"
  },
  {
    "question": "Distribute",
    "answer": "分配"
  },
  {
    "question": "Document",
    "answer": "文件"
  },
  {
    "question": "Donate",
    "answer": "捐贈"
  },
  {
    "question": "Double",
    "answer": "雙倍的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Download",
    "answer": "下載"
  },
  {
    "question": "Downsize",
    "answer": "縮編"
  },
  {
    "question": "Draft",
    "answer": "草稿"
  },
  {
    "question": "Dramatic",
    "answer": "戲劇性的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Drastic",
    "answer": "激烈的"
  },
   {
    "question": "Duration",
    "answer": "持續時間"
  },
  {
    "question": "Earn",
    "answer": "賺取"
  },
  {
    "question": "Economical",
    "answer": "經濟的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Effective",
    "answer": "有效的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Efficient",
    "answer": "有效率的"
  },
   {
    "question": "Elderly",
    "answer": "年長的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Electrical",
    "answer": "電的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Elevator",
    "answer": "電梯"
  },
  {
    "question": "Emergency",
    "answer": "緊急情況"
  },
  {
    "question": "Employ",
    "answer": "僱用"
  },
  {
    "question": "Employee",
    "answer": "員工"
  },
  {
    "question": "Employer",
    "answer": "雇主"
  },
  {
    "question": "Employment",
    "answer": "就業"
  },
  {
    "question": "Enable",
    "answer": "使能夠"
  },
  {
    "question": "Enclose",
    "answer": "隨附"
  },
  {
    "question": "Encourage",
    "answer": "鼓勵"
  },
  {
    "question": "Endure",
    "answer": "忍受"
  },
  {
    "question": "Engineer",
    "answer": "工程師"
  },
  {
    "question": "Engineering",
    "answer": "工程"
  },
  {
    "question": "Enhance",
    "answer": "提高"
  },
  {
    "question": "Enroll",
    "answer": "註冊"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ensure",
    "answer": "確保"
  },
  {
    "question": "Enterprise",
    "answer": "企業"
  },
  {
    "question": "Enthusiastic",
    "answer": "熱情的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Entitlement",
    "answer": "權利"
  },
  {
    "question": "Entry",
    "answer": "入口"
  },
  {
    "question": "Environment",
    "answer": "環境"
  },
  {
    "question": "Equipment",
    "answer": "設備"
  },
  {
    "question": "Equivalent",
    "answer": "同等的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Essential",
    "answer": "必要的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Establish",
    "answer": "建立"
  },
  {
    "question": "Estimate",
    "answer": "估計"
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate",
    "answer": "評估"
  },
  {
    "question": "Evidence",
    "answer": "證據"
  },
  {
    "question": "Evolve",
    "answer": "進化"
  },
  {
    "question": "Exact",
    "answer": "精確的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Examine",
    "answer": "檢查"
  },
  {
    "question": "Excellent",
    "answer": "優秀的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Except",
    "answer": "除了"
  },
  {
    "question": "Exception",
    "answer": "例外"
  },
  {
    "question": "Exchange",
    "answer": "交換"
  },
  {
    "question": "Executive",
    "answer": "行政人員"
  },
  {
    "question": "Exhibit",
    "answer": "展示"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expand",
    "answer": "擴大"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expect",
    "answer": "期望"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expectation",
    "answer": "期望"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expense",
    "answer": "費用"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expensive",
    "answer": "昂貴的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Experience",
    "answer": "經驗"
  },
  {
    "question": "Experienced",
    "answer": "有經驗的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Experiment",
    "answer": "實驗"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expert",
    "answer": "專家"
  },
  {
    "question": "Explain",
    "answer": "解釋"
  },
  {
    "question": "Explore",
    "answer": "探索"
  },
  {
    "question": "Export",
    "answer": "出口"
  },
  {
    "question": "Express",
    "answer": "表達"
  },
  {
    "question": "Extend",
    "answer": "延長"
  },
  {
    "question": "Extension",
    "answer": "延伸"
  },
  {
    "question": "External",
    "answer": "外部的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Facility",
    "answer": "設施"
  },
  {
    "question": "Factor",
    "answer": "因素"
  },
  {
    "question": "Factory",
    "answer": "工廠"
  },
  {
    "question": "Failure",
    "answer": "失敗"
  },
  {
    "question": "Fair",
    "answer": "公平的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Fare",
    "answer": "車資"
  },
  {
    "question": "Fault",
    "answer": "錯誤"
  },
  {
    "question": "Feature",
    "answer": "特色"
  },
  {
    "question": "Fee",
    "answer": "費用"
  },
  {
    "question": "Feedback",
    "answer": "回饋"
  },
  {
    "question": "Figure",
    "answer": "數字"
  },
  {
    "question": "File",
    "answer": "檔案"
  },
  {
    "question": "Finance",
    "answer": "財務"
  },
  {
    "question": "Financial",
    "answer": "財務的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Firm",
    "answer": "公司"
  },
  {
    "question": "Fix",
    "answer": "修理"
  },
  {
    "question": "Flexible",
    "answer": "靈活的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Forecast",
    "answer": "預測"
  },
  {
    "question": "Foreign",
    "answer": "外國的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Form",
    "answer": "表格"
  },
  {
    "question": "Formal",
    "answer": "正式的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Forward",
    "answer": "向前"
  },
  {
    "question": "Foundation",
    "answer": "基礎"
  },
  {
    "question": "Framework",
    "answer": "框架"
  },
  {
    "question": "Frequent",
    "answer": "頻繁的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Frustrated",
    "answer": "沮喪的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Function",
    "answer": "功能"
  },
  {
    "question": "Fundamental",
    "answer": "基本的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Furniture",
    "answer": "家具"
  },
  {
    "question": "Gain",
    "answer": "獲得"
  },
  {
    "question": "Guarantee",
    "answer": "保證"
  },
   {
    "question": "Gather",
    "answer": "聚集"
  },
  {
    "question": "General",
    "answer": "一般的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Generate",
    "answer": "產生"
  },
  {
    "question": "Goal",
    "answer": "目標"
  },
  {
    "question": "Government",
    "answer": "政府"
  },
  {
    "question": "Grant",
    "answer": "授予"
  },
  {
     "question": "Handle",
    "answer": "處理"
  },
  {
    "question": "Headquarters",
    "answer": "總部"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hire",
    "answer": "僱用"
  },
  {
    "question": "Honor",
    "answer": "榮譽"
  },
  {
    "question": "Host",
    "answer": "主辦"
  },
  {
    "question": "Household",
    "answer": "家庭"
  },
  {
    "question": "Huge",
    "answer": "巨大的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ideal",
    "answer": "理想的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Identify",
    "answer": "識別"
  },
  {
    "question": "Implement",
    "answer": "實施"
  },
  {
    "question": "Imply",
    "answer": "暗示"
  },
  {
    "question": "Import",
    "answer": "進口"
  },
  {
    "question": "Improve",
    "answer": "改善"
  },
  {
    "question": "Incentive",
    "answer": "獎勵"
  },
  {
    "question": "Income",
    "answer": "收入"
  },
  {
    "question": "Increase",
    "answer": "增加"
  },
  {
    "question": "Industry",
    "answer": "產業"
  },
  {
    "question": "Influence",
    "answer": "影響"
  },
  {
    "question": "Inform",
    "answer": "通知"
  },
  {
    "question": "Information",
    "answer": "資訊"
  },
  {
    "question": "Initial",
    "answer": "最初的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Initiative",
    "answer": "倡議"
  },
  {
    "question": "Inspect",
    "answer": "檢查"
  },
  {
    "question": "Install",
    "answer": "安裝"
  },
  {
    "question": "Instruction",
    "answer": "指示"
  },
  {
    "question": "Insurance",
    "answer": "保險"
  },
  {
    "question": "Integrate",
    "answer": "整合"
  },
  {
    "question": "Intellectual",
    "answer": "智力的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Intend",
    "answer": "打算"
  },
  {
    "question": "Intensive",
    "answer": "密集的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Interact",
    "answer": "互動"
  },
  {
    "question": "Interest",
    "answer": "興趣"
  },
  {
    "question": "Interim",
    "answer": "暫時的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Internal",
    "answer": "內部的"
  },
  {
    "question": "International",
    "answer": "國際的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Interview",
    "answer": "面試"
  },
  {
    "question": "Introduce",
    "answer": "介紹"
  },
  {
    "question": "Invest",
    "answer": "投資"
  },
  {
    "question": "Investment",
    "answer": "投資"
  },
  {
    "question": "Issue",
    "answer": "議題"
  },
  {
    "question": "Item",
    "answer": "項目"
  },
  {
    "question": "Job",
    "answer": "工作"
  },
  {
    "question": "Journal",
    "answer": "期刊"
  },
  {
    "question": "Journey",
    "answer": "旅程"
  },
  {
    "question": "Judge",
    "answer": "判斷"
  },
  {
    "question": "Justify",
    "answer": "證明...是正當的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Keep",
    "answer": "保持"
  },
  {
    "question": "Key",
    "answer": "關鍵"
  },
  {
    "question": "Knowledge",
    "answer": "知識"
  },
  {
    "question": "Label",
    "answer":"標籤"
  },
  {
    "question": "Labor",
    "answer": "勞工"
  },
  {
    "question": "Lack",
    "answer": "缺乏"
  },
  {
    "question": "Land",
    "answer": "土地"
  },
  {
    "question": "Landscape",
    "answer": "風景"
  },
  {
    "question": "Last",
    "answer": "持續"
  },
  {
    "question": "Latest",
    "answer": "最新的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Launch",
    "answer": "發布"
  },
  {
    "question": "Law",
    "answer": "法律"
  },
  {
    "question": "Layoff",
    "answer": "解雇"
  },
  {
    "question": "Lead",
    "answer": "領導"
  },
  {
    "question": "Leadership",
    "answer": "領導才能"
  },
  {
    "question": "Leading",
    "answer": "領先的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Leak",
    "answer": "洩漏"
  },
  {
    "question": "Leave",
    "answer": "休假"
  },
  {
    "question": "Legal",
    "answer": "法律的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Legislation",
    "answer": "立法"
  },
  {
    "question": "Legitimate",
    "answer": "合法的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Leisure",
    "answer": "休閒"
  },
  {
    "question": "Lend",
    "answer": "借出"
  },
  {
    "question": "Length",
    "answer": "長度"
  },
  {
    "question": "Less",
    "answer": "較少的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Level",
    "answer": "水平"
  },
  {
    "question": "License",
    "answer": "執照"
  },
  {
    "question": "Limit",
    "answer": "限制"
  },
  {
    "question": "Line",
    "answer": "線"
  },
  {
    "question": "Liquid",
    "answer": "液體"
  },
  {
    "question": "List",
    "answer": "清單"
  },
  {
    "question": "Loan",
    "answer": "貸款"
  },
  {
    "question": "Local",
    "answer": "當地的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Locate",
    "answer": "位於"
  },
  {
    "question": "Location",
    "answer": "地點"
  },
  {
    "question": "Logic",
    "answer": "邏輯"
  },
  {
    "question": "Long-term",
    "answer": "長期的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Loss",
    "answer": "損失"
  },
  {
    "question": "Maintain",
    "answer": "維持"
  },
  {
    "question": "Maintenance",
    "answer": "維修"
  },
  {
    "question": "Major",
    "answer": "主要的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Majority",
    "answer": "多數"
  },
  {
    "question": "Manage",
    "answer": "管理"
  },
  {
    "question": "Management",
    "answer": "管理"
  },
  {
    "question": "Manager",
    "answer": "經理"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mandatory",
    "answer": "強制的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Manufacture",
    "answer": "製造"
  },
  {
    "question": "Manufacturer",
    "answer": "製造商"
  },
  {
    "question": "Manufacturing",
    "answer": "製造業"
  },
  {
    "question": "Market",
    "answer": "市場"
  },
  {
    "question": "Marketing",
    "answer": "行銷"
  },
  {
    "question": "Material",
    "answer": "材料"
  },
  {
    "question": "Measure",
    "answer": "測量"
  },
  {
    "question": "Media",
    "answer": "媒體"
  },
  {
    "question": "Meet",
    "answer": "滿足"
  },
  {
    "question": "Meeting",
    "answer": "會議"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mention",
    "answer": "提及"
  },
  {
    "question": "Merchandise",
    "answer": "商品"
  },
  {
    "question": "Merge",
    "answer": "合併"
  },
  {
    "question": "Method",
    "answer": "方法"
  },
  {
    "question": "Migrate",
    "answer": "遷移"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mile",
    "answer": "英里"
  },
  {
    "question": "Minimize",
    "answer": "最小化"
  },
  {
    "question": "Minimum",
    "answer": "最小的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mislead",
    "answer": "誤導"
  },
  {
    "question": "Miss",
    "answer": "錯過"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mission",
    "answer": "任務"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mistake",
    "answer": "錯誤"
  },
  {
    "question": "Modify",
    "answer": "修改"
  },
  {
    "question": "Monitor",
    "answer": "監控"
  },
  {
    "question": "Monthly",
    "answer": "每月的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mortgage",
    "answer": "抵押"
  },
  {
    "question": "Motivate",
    "answer": "激勵"
  },
  {
    "question": "Motive",
    "answer": "動機"
  },
  {
    "question": "Move",
    "answer": "移動"
  },
  {
    "question": "Negotiate",
    "answer": "談判"
  },
  {
    "question": "Network",
    "answer": "網絡"
  },
  {
    "question": "Neutral",
    "answer": "中立的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Nevertheless",
    "answer": "儘管如此"
  },
  {
    "question": "New",
    "answer": "新的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Newly",
    "answer": "新地"
  },
  {
    "question": "Next",
    "answer": "下一個"
  },
  {
    "question": "Normally",
    "answer": "通常"
  },
  {
    "question": "Notice",
    "answer": "注意"
  },
  {
    "question": "Notify",
    "answer": "通知"
  },
  {
    "question": "Numerous",
    "answer": "眾多的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Object",
    "answer": "反對"
  },
  {
    "question": "Objective",
    "answer": "目標"
  },
  {
    "question": "Obligation",
    "answer": "義務"
  },
  {
    "question": "Observe",
    "answer": "觀察"
  },
  {
    "question": "Obtain",
    "answer": "獲得"
  },
  {
    "question": "Occupy",
    "answer": "佔據"
  },
  {
    "question": "Occur",
    "answer": "發生"
  },
  {
    "question": "Offer",
    "answer": "提供"
  },
  {
    "question": "Official",
    "answer": "官方的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Operate",
    "answer": "操作"
  },
  {
    "question": "Operation",
    "answer": "操作"
  },
  {
    "question": "Opportunity",
    "answer": "機會"
  },
  {
    "question": "Option",
    "answer": "選項"
  },
  {
    "question": "Order",
    "answer": "訂購"
  },
  {
    "question": "Organize",
    "answer": "組織"
  },
  {
    "question": "Original",
    "answer": "原始的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Other",
    "answer": "其他的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Overall",
    "answer": "總的來說"
  },
  {
    "question": "Overtime",
    "answer": "加班"
  },
  {
    "question": "Owner",
    "answer": "所有者"
  },
  {
    "question": "Package",
    "answer": "包裹"
  },
  {
    "question": "Page",
    "answer": "頁"
  },
  {
    "question": "Panel",
    "answer": "面板"
  },
  {
    "question": "Paper",
    "answer": "紙"
  },
  {
    "question": "Paragraph",
    "answer": "段落"
  },
  {
    "question": "Parcel",
    "answer": "包裹"
  },
  {
    "question": "Part",
    "answer": "部分"
  },
  {
    "question": "Particular",
    "answer": "特定的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Party",
    "answer": "派對"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pass",
    "answer": "通過"
  },
  {
    "question": "Passenger",
    "answer": "乘客"
  },
  {
    "question": "Passport",
    "answer": "護照"
  },
  {
    "question": "Past",
    "answer": "過去"
  },
  {
    "question": "Path",
    "answer": "路徑"
  },
  {
    "question": "Patient",
    "answer": "有耐心的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pattern",
    "answer": "模式"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pay",
    "answer": "支付"
  },
  {
    "question": "Payment",
    "answer": "支付"
  },
  {
    "question": "Penalty",
    "answer": "罰款"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pending",
    "answer": "待定的"
  },
  {
    "question": "People",
    "answer": "人"
  },
  {
    "question": "Percent",
    "answer": "百分比"
  },
  {
    "question": "Percentage",
    "answer": "百分比"
  },
  {
    "question": "Perform",
    "answer": "執行"
  },
  {
    "question": "Performance",
    "answer": "性能"
  },
  {
    "question": "Period",
    "answer": "期間"
  },
  {
    "question": "Permit",
    "answer": "允許"
  },
  {
    "question": "Person",
    "answer": "人"
  },
  {
    "question": "Personal",
    "answer": "個人的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Personnel",
    "answer": "人事"
  },
  {
    "question": "Persuade",
    "answer": "說服"
  },
  {
    "question": "Phase",
    "answer": "階段"
  },
  {
    "question": "Phone",
    "answer": "電話"
  },
  {
    "question": "Photograph",
    "answer": "照片"
  },
  {
    "question": "Phrase",
    "answer": "片語"
  },
  {
    "question": "Physical",
    "answer": "身體的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pick",
    "answer": "挑選"
  },
  {
    "question": "Piece",
    "answer": "塊"
  },
  {
    "question": "Place",
    "answer": "地點"
  },
  {
    "question": "Plan",
    "answer": "計劃"
  },
  {
    "question": "Plant",
    "answer": "植物"
  },
  {
    "question": "Platform",
    "answer": "平台"
  },
  {
    "question": "Policy",
    "answer": "政策"
  },
  {
    "question": "Position",
    "answer": "位置"
  },
  {
    "question": "Possess",
    "answer": "擁有"
  },
  {
    "question": "Possibility",
    "answer": "可能性"
  },
  {
    "question": "Possible",
    "answer": "可能的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Post",
    "answer": "張貼"
  },
  {
    "question": "Postpone",
    "answer": "延後"
  },
  {
    "question": "Potential",
    "answer": "潛在的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Power",
    "answer": "力量"
  },
  {
    "question": "Practice",
    "answer": "練習"
  },
  {
    "question": "Praise",
    "answer": "讚揚"
  },
  {
    "question": "Predict",
    "answer": "預測"
  },
  {
    "question": "Prefer",
    "answer": "偏好"
  },
  {
    "question": "Preference",
    "answer": "偏好"
  },
  {
    "question": "Prepare",
    "answer": "準備"
  },
  {
    "question": "Presence",
    "answer": "出席"
  },
  {
    "question": "Present",
    "answer": "呈現"
  },
  {
    "question": "Presentation",
    "answer": "簡報"
  },
  {
    "question": "Preserve",
    "answer": "保存"
  },
  {
    "question": "President",
    "answer": "總統"
  },
  {
    "question": "Press",
    "answer": "按壓"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pressure",
    "answer": "壓力"
  },
  {
    "question": "Previous",
    "answer": "先前的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Price",
    "answer": "價格"
  },
  {
    "question": "Primary",
    "answer": "主要的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Principal",
    "answer": "主要的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Principle",
    "answer": "原則"
  },
  {
    "question": "Prior",
    "answer": "先前的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Priority",
    "answer": "優先"
  },
  {
    "question": "Private",
    "answer": "私人的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Prize",
    "answer": "獎品"
  },
  {
    "question": "Problem",
    "answer": "問題"
  },
  {
    "question": "Procedure",
    "answer": "程序"
  },
  {
    "question": "Process",
    "answer": "過程"
  },
  {
    "question": "Produce",
    "answer": "生產"
  },
  {
    "question": "Product",
    "answer": "產品"
  },
  {
    "question": "Production",
    "answer": "生產"
  },
  {
    "question": "Profession",
    "answer": "職業"
  },
  {
    "question": "Professional",
    "answer": "專業的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Profit",
    "answer": "利潤"
  },
  {
    "question": "Program",
    "answer": "節目"
  },
  {
    "question": "Project",
    "answer": "項目"
  },
  {
    "question": "Promise",
    "answer": "承諾"
  },
  {
    "question": "Promote",
    "answer": "促進"
  },
  {
    "question": "Promotion",
    "answer": "促銷"
  },
  {
    "question": "Proposal",
    "answer": "提案"
  },
  {
    "question": "Propose",
    "answer": "提議"
  },
  {
    "question": "Prospect",
    "answer": "前景"
  },
  {
    "question": "Provide",
    "answer": "提供"
  },
  {
    "question": "Public",
    "answer": "公開的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Publish",
    "answer": "出版"
  },
  {
    "question": "Purchase",
    "answer": "購買"
  },
  {
    "question": "Purpose",
    "answer": "目的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pursue",
    "answer": "追求"
  },
  {
    "question": "Quality",
    "answer": "品質"
  },
  {
    "question": "Quantity",
    "answer": "數量"
  },
  {
    "question": "Quarter",
    "answer": "季度"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question",
    "answer": "問題"
  },
  {
    "question": "Quite",
    "answer": "相當"
  },
  {
    "question": "Raise",
    "answer": "提高"
  },
  {
    "question": "Range",
    "answer": "範圍"
  },
  {
    "question": "Rate",
    "answer": "比率"
  },
  {
    "question": "Rather",
    "answer": "寧願"
  },
  {
    "question": "Reach",
    "answer": "達到"
  },
  {
    "question": "Read",
    "answer": "讀"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ready",
    "answer": "準備好的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Real",
    "answer": "真的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Realize",
    "answer": "實現"
  },
  {
    "question": "Reason",
    "answer": "原因"
  },
  {
    "question": "Recall",
    "answer": "回想"
  },
  {
    "question": "Receive",
    "answer": "收到"
  },
  {
    "question": "Recent",
    "answer": "最近的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Recently",
    "answer": "最近"
  },
  {
    "question": "Reception",
    "answer": "接待"
  },
  {
    "question": "Recognize",
    "answer": "認出"
  },
  {
    "question": "Recommend",
    "answer": "推薦"
  },
  {
    "question": "Record",
    "answer": "記錄"
  },
  {
    "question": "Reduce",
    "answer": "減少"
  },
  {
    "question": "Refer",
    "answer": "參考"
  },
  {
    "question": "Reference",
    "answer": "參考"
  },
  {
    "question": "Reflect",
    "answer": "反映"
  },
  {
    "question": "Refund",
    "answer": "退款"
  },
  {
    "question": "Refuse",
    "answer": "拒絕"
  },
  {
    "question": "Regarding",
    "answer": "關於"
  },
  {
    "question": "Register",
    "answer": "註冊"
  },
  {
    "question": "Regret",
    "answer": "後悔"
  },
  {
    "question": "Regular",
    "answer": "規律的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Regulate",
    "answer": " регулировать"
  },
  {
    "question": "Regulation",
    "answer": "規定"
  },
  {
    "question": "Reinforce",
    "answer": "加強"
  },
  {
    "question": "Reject",
    "answer": "拒絕"
  },
  {
    "question": "Relate",
    "answer": "相關"
  },
  {
    "question": "Relative",
    "answer": "相對的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Release",
    "answer": "發布"
  },
  {
    "question": "Relevant",
    "answer": "相關的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Reliable",
    "answer": "可靠的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Relieve",
    "answer": "減輕"
  },
  {
    "question": "Relocation",
    "answer": "遷移"
  },
  {
    "question": "Remain",
    "answer": "保持"
  },
  {
    "question": "Remark",
    "answer": "評論"
  },
  {
    "question": "Remember",
    "answer": "記得"
  },
  {
    "question": "Remind",
    "answer": "提醒"
  },
  {
    "question": "Remove",
    "answer": "移除"
  },
  {
    "question": "Rent",
    "answer": "租"
  },
  {
    "question": "Repair",
    "answer": "修理"
  },
  {
    "question": "Repeat",
    "answer": "重複"
  },
  {
    "question": "Replace",
    "answer": "取代"
  },
  {
    "question": "Reply",
    "answer": "回覆"
  },
  {
    "question": "Report",
    "answer": "報告"
  },
  {
    "question": "Represent",
    "answer": "代表"
  },
  {
    "question": "Request",
    "answer": "要求"
  },
  {
    "question": "Require",
    "answer": "需要"
  },
  {
    "question": "Requirement",
    "answer": "要求"
  },
  {
    "question": "Research",
    "answer": "研究"
  },
  {
    "question": "Resign",
    "answer": "辭職"
  },
  {
    "question": "Resist",
    "answer": "抵抗"
  },
  {
    "question": "Resolve",
    "answer": "解決"
  },
  {
    "question": "Resource",
    "answer": "資源"
  },
  {
    "question": "Respond",
    "answer": "回應"
  },
  {
    "question": "Response",
    "answer": "回應"
  },
  {
    "question": "Responsible",
    "answer": "負責的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Rest",
    "answer": "休息"
  },
  {
    "question": "Restaurant",
    "answer": "餐廳"
  },
  {
    "question": "Restrict",
    "answer": "限制"
  },
  {
    "question": "Result",
    "answer": "結果"
  },
  {
    "question": "Retail",
    "answer": "零售"
  },
  {
    "question": "Retain",
    "answer": "保留"
  },
  {
    "question": "Return","answer": "返回"
  },
  {
    "question": "Review",
    "answer": "複習"
  },
  {
    "question": "Revise",
    "answer": "修改"
  },
  {
    "question": "Risk",
    "answer": "風險"
  },
  {
    "question": "Role",
    "answer": "角色"
  },
  {
    "question": "Room",
    "answer": "房間"
  },
  {
    "question": "Route",
    "answer": "路線"
  },
  {
    "question": "Routine",
    "answer": "例行公事"
  },
  {
    "question": "Rule",
    "answer": "規則"
  },
  {
    "question": "Run",
    "answer": "跑"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sale",
    "answer": "銷售"
  },
  {
    "question": "Salary",
    "answer": "薪水"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sample",
    "answer": "樣本"
  },
  {
    "question": "Save",
    "answer": "儲存"
  },
  {
    "question": "Schedule",
    "answer": "行程"
  },
  {
    "question": "Scheme",
    "answer": "計劃"
  },
  {
    "question": "Search",
    "answer": "搜尋"
  },
  {
    "question": "Season",
    "answer": "季節"
  },
  {
    "question": "Seat",
    "answer": "座位"
  },
  {
    "question": "Second",
    "answer": "第二"
  },
  {
    "question": "Section",
    "answer": "部分"
  },
  {
    "question": "Security",
    "answer": "安全"
  },
  {
    "question": "Seek",
    "answer": "尋求"
  },
  {
    "question": "Select",
    "answer": "選擇"
  },
  {
    "question": "Selection",
    "answer": "選擇"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sell",
    "answer": "賣"
  },
  {
    "question": "Send",
    "answer": "寄送"
  },
  {
    "question": "Senior",
    "answer": "資深的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sense",
    "answer": "感覺"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sensitive",
    "answer": "敏感的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Separate",
    "answer": "分開的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Series",
    "answer": "系列"
  },
  {
    "question": "Serious",
    "answer": "嚴重的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Serve",
    "answer": "服務"
  },
  {
    "question": "Service",
    "answer": "服務"
  },
  {
    "question": "Session",
    "answer": "會議"
  },
  {
    "question": "Set",
    "answer": "設定"
  },
  {
    "question": "Settle",
    "answer": "解決"
  },
  {
    "question": "Severe",
    "answer": "嚴重的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Share",
    "answer": "分享"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sheet",
    "answer": "表格"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ship",
    "answer": "運送"
  },
  {
    "question": "Short",
    "answer": "短的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Shortage",
    "answer": "短缺"
  },
  {
    "question": "Should",
    "answer": "應該"
  },
  {
    "question": "Show",
    "answer": "展示"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sign",
    "answer": "簽名"
  },
  {
    "question": "Signal",
    "answer": "信號"
  },
  {
    "question": "Significant",
    "answer": "重要的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Similar",
    "answer": "相似的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Simple",
    "answer": "簡單的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Since",
    "answer": "自從"
  },
  {
    "question": "Situation",
    "answer": "情況"
  },
  {
    "question": "Size",
    "answer": "大小"
  },
  {
    "question": "Skill",
    "answer": "技能"
  },
  {
    "question": "Slight",
    "answer": "輕微的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Slip",
    "answer": "滑倒"
  },
  {
    "question": "Slow",
    "answer": "慢的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Solution",
    "answer": "解決方案"
  },
  {
    "question": "Solve",
    "answer": "解決"
  },
  {
    "question": "Some",
    "answer": "一些"
  },
  {
    "question": "Someone",
    "answer": "某人"
  },
  {
    "question": "Something",
    "answer": "某事"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sometimes",
    "answer": "有時"
  },
  {
    "question": "Somewhere",
    "answer": "某處"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sort",
    "answer": "排序"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sound",
    "answer": "聲音"
  },
  {
    "question": "Source",
    "answer": "來源"
  },
  {
    "question": "Space",
    "answer": "空間"
  },
  {
    "question": "Speak",
    "answer": "說"
  },
  {
    "question": "Special",
    "answer": "特別的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Specific",
    "answer": "特定的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Specify",
    "answer": "指定"
  },
  {
    "question": "Speed",
    "answer": "速度"
  },
  {
    "question": "Spend",
    "answer": "花費"
  },
  {
    "question": "Staff",
    "answer": "員工"
  },
  {
    "question": "Stage",
    "answer": "階段"
  },
  {
    "question": "Standard",
    "answer": "標準"
  },
  {
    "question": "Start",
    "answer": "開始"
  },
  {
    "question": "State",
    "answer": "狀態"
  },
  {
    "question": "Statement",
    "answer": "聲明"
  },
  {
    "question": "Station",
    "answer": "車站"
  },
  {
    "question": "Status",
    "answer": "狀態"
  },
  {
    "question": "Stay",
    "answer": "停留"
  },
  {
    "question": "Step",
    "answer": "步驟"
  },
  {
    "question": "Stick",
    "answer": "黏住"
  },
  {
    "question": "Still",
    "answer": "仍然"
  },
  {
    "question": "Stock",
    "answer": "庫存"
  },
  {
    "question": "Stop",
    "answer": "停止"
  },
  {
    "question": "Store",
    "answer": "商店"
  },
  {
    "question": "Story",
    "answer": "故事"
  },
  {
    "question": "Strategy",
    "answer": "策略"
  },
  {
    "question": "Stress",
    "answer": "壓力"
  },
  {
    "question": "Strict",
    "answer": "嚴格的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Structure",
    "answer": "結構"
  },
  {
    "question": "Student",
    "answer": "學生"
  },
  {
    "question": "Study",
    "answer": "學習"
  },
  {
    "question": "Style",
    "answer": "風格"
  },
  {
    "question": "Subject",
    "answer": "主題"
  },
  {
    "question": "Submit",
    "answer": "提交"
  },
  {
    "question": "Subsequent",
    "answer": "隨後的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Subsidy",
    "answer": "補助金"
  },
  {
    "question": "Substance",
    "answer": "物質"
  },
  {
    "question": "Substantial",
    "answer": "大量的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Succeed",
    "answer": "成功"
  },
  {
    "question": "Success",
    "answer": "成功"
  },
  {
    "question": "Successful",
    "answer": "成功的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Such",
    "answer": "這樣的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sudden",
    "answer": "突然的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Suddenly",
    "answer": "突然地"
  },
  {
    "question": "Suggest",
    "answer": "建議"
  },
  {
    "question": "Suggestion",
    "answer": "建議"
  },
  {
    "question": "Suit",
    "answer": "適合"
  },
  {
    "question": "Suitable",
    "answer": "適合的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sum",
    "answer": "總和"
  },
  {
    "question": "Summarize",
    "answer": "總結"
  },
  {
    "question": "Summary",
    "answer": "總結"
  },
  {
    "question": "Supply",
    "answer": "供應"
  },
  {
    "question": "Support",
    "answer": "支持"
  },
  {
    "question": "Suppose",
    "answer": "假設"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sure",
    "answer": "確定的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Surface",
    "answer": "表面"
  },
  {
    "question": "Surprise",
    "answer": "驚訝"
  },
  {
    "question": "Surround",
    "answer": "包圍"
  },
  {
    "question": "Survey",
    "answer": "調查"
  },
  {
    "question": "Switch",
    "answer": "開關"
  },
  {
    "question": "System",
    "answer": "系統"
  },
  {
    "question": "Table",
    "answer": "表格"
  },
  {
    "question": "Take",
    "answer": "拿"
  },
  {
    "question": "Talent",
    "answer": "天賦"
  },
  {
    "question": "Talk",
    "answer": "說話"
  },
  {
    "question": "Task",
    "answer": "任務"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tax",
    "answer": "稅"
  },
  {
    "question": "Team",
    "answer": "團隊"
  },
  {
    "question": "Technical",
    "answer": "技術的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Technique",
    "answer": "技術"
  },
  {
    "question": "Technology",
    "answer": "科技"
  },
  {
    "question": "Telephone",
    "answer": "電話"
  },
  {
    "question": "Temporary",
    "answer": "臨時的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ten",
    "answer": "十"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tend",
    "answer": "傾向於"
  },
  {
    "question": "Term",
    "answer": "術語"
  },
  {
    "question": "Terminal",
    "answer": "航廈"
  },
  {
    "question": "Test",
    "answer": "測試"
  },
  {
    "question": "Text",
    "answer": "文本"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thank",
    "answer": "謝謝"
  },
  {
    "question": "That",
    "answer": "那"
  },
  {
    "question": "The",
    "answer": "這"
  },
  {
    "question": "Their",
    "answer": "他們的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Them",
    "answer": "他們"
  },
  {
    "question": "Then",
    "answer": "然後"
  },
  {
    "question": "There",
    "answer": "那裡"
  },
  {
    "question": "Therefore",
    "answer": "因此"
  },
  {
    "question": "These",
    "answer": "這些"
  },
  {
    "question": "They",
    "answer": "他們"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thing",
    "answer": "事情"
  },
  {
    "question": "Think",
    "answer": "想"
  },
  {
    "question": "Third",
    "answer": "第三"
  },
  {
    "question": "This",
    "answer": "這個"
  },
  {
    "question": "Those",
    "answer": "那些"
  },
  {
    "question": "Though",
    "answer": "雖然"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thought",
    "answer": "想法"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thousand",
    "answer": "千"
  },
  {
    "question": "Threat",
    "answer": "威脅"
  },
  {
    "question": "Through",
    "answer": "通過"
  },
  {
    "question": "Throughout",
    "answer": "貫穿"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thus",
    "answer": "因此"
  },
  {
    "question": "Time",
    "answer": "時間"
  },
  {
    "question": "Title",
    "answer": "標題"
  },
  {
    "question": "Today",
    "answer": "今天"
  },
  {
    "question": "Together",
    "answer": "一起"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tomorrow",
    "answer": "明天"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tonight",
    "answer": "今晚"
  },
  {
    "question": "Too",
    "answer": "也"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tool",
    "answer": "工具"
  },
  {
    "question": "Top",
    "answer": "頂部"
  },
  {
    "question": "Total",
    "answer": "總計"
  },
  {
    "question": "Touch",
    "answer": "觸摸"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tour",
    "answer": "旅行"
  },
  {
    "question": "Toward",
    "answer": "朝向"
  },
  {
    "question": "Town",
    "answer": "城鎮"
  },
  {
    "question": "Trade",
    "answer": "貿易"
  },
  {
    "question": "Traditional",
    "answer": "傳統的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Traffic",
    "answer": "交通"
  },
  {
    "question": "Train",
    "answer": "火車"
  },
  {
    "question": "Training",
    "answer": "訓練"
  },
  {
    "question": "Transfer",
    "answer": "轉移"
  },
  {
    "question": "Transform",
    "answer": "轉變"
  },
  {
    "question": "Transition",
    "answer": "轉變"
  },
  {
    "question": "Translate",
    "answer": "翻譯"
  },
  {
    "question": "Transportation",
    "answer": "運輸"
  },
  {
    "question": "Travel",
    "answer": "旅行"
  },
  {
    "question": "Treat",
    "answer": "對待"
  },
  {
    "question": "Treatment",
    "answer": "治療"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tree",
    "answer": "樹"
  },
  {
    "question": "Trend",
    "answer": "趨勢"
  },
  {
    "question": "Trial",
    "answer": "審判"
  },
  {
    "question": "Trip",
    "answer": "旅行"
  },
  {
    "question": "Trouble",
    "answer": "麻煩"
  },
  {
    "question": "True",
    "answer": "真的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Trust",
    "answer": "信任"
  },
  {
    "question": "Truth",
    "answer": "真相"
  },
  {
    "question": "Try",
    "answer": "嘗試"
  },
  {
    "question": "Turn",
    "answer": "轉"
  },
  {
    "question": "Type",
    "answer": "類型"
  },
  {
    "question": "Typical",
    "answer": "典型的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Under",
    "answer": "在...之下"
  },
  {
    "question": "Understand",
    "answer": "理解"
  },
  {
    "question": "Understanding",
    "answer": "理解"
  },
  {
    "question": "Undertake",
    "answer": "承擔"
  },
  {
    "question": "Unemployment",
    "answer": "失業"
  },
  {
    "question": "Unexpected",
    "answer": "意想不到的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Unique",
    "answer": "獨特的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Unit",
    "answer": "單位"
  },
  {
    "question": "Universal",
    "answer": "普遍的"
  },
  {
    "question": "University",
    "answer": "大學"
  },
  {
    "question": "Unless",
    "answer": "除非"
  },
  {
    "question": "Unlike",
    "answer": "不像"
  },
  {
    "question": "Unlikely",
    "answer": "不太可能的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Until",
    "answer": "直到"
  },
  {
    "question": "Up",
    "answer": "向上"
  },
  {
    "question": "Update",
    "answer": "更新"
  },
  {
    "question": "Upon",
    "answer": "在...之上"
  },
  {
    "question": "Upper",
    "answer": "上面的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Urgent",
    "answer": "緊急的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Us",
    "answer": "我們"
  },
  {
    "question": "Use",
    "answer": "使用"
  },
  {
    "question": "Used",
    "answer": "用過的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Useful",
    "answer": "有用的"
  },
  {
    "question": "User",
    "answer": "用戶"
  },
  {
    "question": "Usually",
    "answer": "通常"
  },
  {
    "question": "Utility",
    "answer": "效用"
  },
  {
    "question": "Vacation",
    "answer": "假期"
  },
  {
    "question": "Valid",
    "answer": "有效的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Value",
    "answer": "價值"
  },
  {
    "question": "Various",
    "answer": "各種的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Variety",
    "answer": "多樣性"
  },
  {
    "question": "Vehicle",
    "answer": "車輛"
  },
  {
    "question": "Version",
    "answer": "版本"
  },
  {
    "question": "Very",
    "answer": "非常"
  },
  {
    "question": "Via",
    "answer": "通過"
  },
  {
    "question": "View",
    "answer": "觀點"
  },
  {
    "question": "Village",
    "answer": "村莊"
  },
  {
    "question": "Visit",
    "answer": "拜訪"
  },
  {
    "question": "Visitor",
    "answer": "訪客"
  },
  {
    "question": "Vital",
    "answer": "重要的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Voice",
    "answer": "聲音"
  },
  {
    "question": "Volume",
    "answer": "音量"
  },
  {
    "question": "Volunteer",
    "answer": "自願者"
  },
  {
    "question": "Vote",
    "answer": "投票"
  },
  {
    "question": "Wait",
    "answer": "等待"
  },
  {
    "question": "Walk",
    "answer": "走"
  },
  {
    "question": "Wall",
    "answer": "牆"
  },
  {
    "question": "Want",
    "answer": "想要"
  },
  {
    "question": "War",
    "answer": "戰爭"
  },
  {
    "question": "Warn",
    "answer": "警告"
  },
  {
    "question": "Wash",
    "answer": "洗"
  },
  {
    "question": "Waste",
    "answer": "浪費"
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch",
    "answer": "觀看"
  },
  {
    "question": "Water",
    "answer": "水"
  },
  {
    "question": "Way",
    "answer": "方法"
  },
  {
    "question": "We",
    "answer": "我們"
  },
  {
    "question": "Weak",
    "answer": "虛弱的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Week",
    "answer": "週"
  },
  {
    "question": "Weekly",
    "answer": "每週的"
  },
  {
    "question": "Weight",
    "answer": "重量"
  },
  {
    "question": "Welcome",
    "answer": "歡迎"
  },
  {
    "question": "Well",
    "answer": "好"
  },
  {
    "question": "West",
    "answer": "西方"
  },
  {
    "question": "What",
    "answer": "什麼"
  },
  {
    "question": "When",
    "answer": "當"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where",
    "answer": "哪裡"
  },
  {
    "question": "Whether",
    "answer": "是否"
  }
]